Erfan Ghezelbash

E-mail: erfan.ghezelbash@gmail.com Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/erfanghezelbash

Phone: +989359886841 Address: Tehran, Iran

Summary

Graduated in software engineering with more than eight years of experience in web programming, intrested and active in Blockchain, Fintech and any other edge technology. Able to build projects from scratch and implement MVP systems with more than 7 successful experiences.

Work experience

Excoino Jun 2019 — Present

Senior Software Engineer

- Change and improve about 80% of the project with the aim of converting the MVP model into enterprise software within a year
- Redesigned data model and software architecture, which increased system performance 6 times
- Increase the test coverage of sensitive parts of the system from zero to 47%
- Support 8 Junior Developers in 18 months by recommending, coaching and routing for research

Dunab Ertebat LLC

Sep 2017 — May 2019

Senior Software Engineer

- Launching 4 startup projects in various fields of finance, cryptocurrency, human resources and project management
- Work on three programming languages: PHP, Java and Nodejs to implement projects
- Interview with more than 100 people in one year and recruit 11 technical staff for the company
- · Coaching, routing and assisting younger techies

Gilas

Co-founder and Software Developer

Jul 2015 — Sep 2017

- Co-founding and developing 3 startup / experimental projects in two years
- Delivery and support of more than 20 customer-oriented projects in the form of an 8-member team
- Providing 4 long-term training courses for web programming enthusiasts for a total of about 60 people

Fara Computer

Feb 2013 — May 2015

Junior Web Developer

 Development and support of company website and two partner companies using WordPress tool as well as Laravel framework

Fara Computer

Jan 2012 — Feb 2013

Software Solutions Support

Fara Computer

Jun 2011 — Jan 2012

Software Internship

Erfan Ghezelbash 1

Education

BSc in Software Engineering

Payame Noor University

Sep 2008 — Jun 2013

Languages

- English Full Professional Proficiency
- Persian/Farsi Native or Bilingual Proficiency
- French Elementry Proficiency

Skills

PHP

Laravel

Blockchain

Solidity

Cryptocurrency

SQL

Teamwork

Technical Coaching

Working under Pressure

Erfan Ghezelbash